=Ex-Wife Stop Ⅱ=
= توقف الزوجة السابقة Ⅱ =
=Episode 7=
= الحلقة 7 =
See?
يرى؟
I told you I'm not drunk.
قلت لك إنني لست في حالة سكر.
Sheng Nanfang.
شنغ نانفانغ.
I'm wide awake now.
أنا مستيقظ للغاية الآن.
I swear
أقسم
I will protect you, take care of you
سأحميك ، اعتني بك
and make you the happiest man
وتجعلك أسعد رجل
in the world.
فى العالم.
Su Shaoyan, do you really love me
سو شاويان ، هل تحبني حقًا
or do you have other intentions?
أو هل لديك نوايا أخرى؟
(Su Shaoyan.)
(سو شاويان.)
(You're totally a loser as a woman.)
(أنت خاسر تمامًا كامرأة.)
(Ms. Su, something really bad happened.)
(السيدة سو ، حدث شيء سيء حقًا.)
What is it?
ما هذا؟
(Mr. Hu suddenly changed his mind. He won't renew his contract with us.)
(غير السيد هو رأيه فجأة. ولن يجدد عقده معنا).
Got it.
فهمتها.
I'll deal with it right away.
سوف أتعامل معها على الفور.
Breakfast's ready.
الفطور جاهز.
Tell your mother to come for breakfast.
أخبر والدتك أن تأتي لتناول الإفطار.
She left.
لقد غادرت.
She left? Where did she go?
لقد غادرت؟  إلى أين ذهبت؟
On a business trip. She won't be back for a few days.
في رحلة عمل.  لن تعود لبضعة أيام.
Mr. Hu.
السيد.  هاه.
I am really sorry for this matter.
أنا حقا آسف لهذا الأمر.
I have already criticized Zhang Tian.
لقد انتقدت بالفعل تشانغ تيان.
Could you please give us another chance?
هل يمكنك أن تعطينا فرصة أخرى من فضلك؟
This time, I'll see you in person.
هذه المرة ، سأراك شخصيًا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
(Have you arrived, Yan?)
(هل وصلت يا يان؟)
Dad.
أب.
Are you waiting to hear from Mom?
هل تنتظر أن تسمع من أمي؟
No.
لا.
I'm waiting
أنا منتظر
for an important message about work.
لرسالة مهمة عن العمل.
You're lying.
انت تكذب.
You just miss Mom.
أنت فقط تفتقد أمي.
But
لكن
I miss her too.
أشتاق لها أيضا.
Why don't we give her a call?
لماذا لا نتصل بها؟
Okay.
تمام.
Then you tell her
ثم أخبرها
it's you who want to make the call.
أنت من تريد إجراء المكالمة.
Got it.
فهمتها.
(Su Shaoyan)
(سو شاويان)
Hello, Mom.
مرحبا امي.
(What are you doing, Crescent?)
(ماذا تفعل يا الهلال؟)
I'm building blocks with Dad.
أنا أبني مع أبي.
(Good girl.)
(فتاة جيدة.)
When will you come back?
عندما تعود؟
Mom.
أم.
Dad wants you back home as soon as you finish work.
أبي يريدك أن تعود إلى المنزل بمجرد الانتهاء من العمل.
He misses you.
انه يفتقدك.
(Really?)
(حقًا؟)
(I miss you too.)
(أفتقدك أيضًا.)
(I'll fly home)
(سأطير إلى المنزل)
(as soon as I'm done here.)
(بمجرد أن انتهيت من هنا.)
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You are here, Yan.
أنت هنا يا (يان).
Come and sit here.
تعال واجلس هنا.
(Jiang Jiayu? Shouldn't he be abroad?)
(جيانغ جيايو؟ ألا يجب أن يكون في الخارج؟)
Mr. Hu.
السيد.  هاه.
Ms. Su.
آنسة.  مع.
I've already told Zhang Tian my decision.
لقد أخبرت بالفعل تشانغ تيان بقراري.
He doesn't know any better.
لا يعرف أي شيء أفضل.
Please excuse his manners.
يرجى المعذرة على أخلاقه.
Now I'm here myself to make amends.
الآن أنا هنا بنفسي للتعويض.
Mr. Hu, let me propose a toast to you.
السيد هو ، دعني أقترح عليك نخبًا.
Wait.
انتظر.
We drink liquor
نشرب الخمور
when we do business in Liucheng.
عندما نقوم بأعمال تجارية في Liucheng.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Wait.
انتظر.
Mr. Hu, here is the thing.
السيد هو ، هذا هو الشيء.
Ms. Su
آنسة.  مع
is an old acquaintance of mine.
هو أحد معارفي القدامى.
Do me a favor, please.
اعمل لي معروف من فضلك.
I'll drink it for her.
سأشربه لها.
You...
أنت...
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
I'll drink
سأشرب
this glass of liquor too.
هذا كأس من الخمور أيضا.
After all, it's our fault.
بعد كل شيء ، هذا خطأنا.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
If you are still not satisfied,
إذا كنت لا تزال غير راضٍ ،
I'll drink one more.
سأشرب واحدة أخرى.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Take a seat.
اجلس.